Ledio Dylgjeri

Full Stack Software Developer

Flushing, NY | (646)578-3908 | lediodylgjeri@gmail.com | GitHub | LinkedIn

Career Objective

My calling in life has been to help people. Coming from a law enforcement background I have had the pleasure to help many by wearing different hats. The experience I gained in problem solving will reflect in my software engineering career. Through technology, I want to continue my work by being involved with future projects that advance humanity.

SKILLS

Programing Languages: JavaScript, Python

Markup/Style Language: HTML, CSS

• Runtime Environment: Node.js

Frameworks: Bootstrap, Express.js, Mongoose, Django, Docker

Databases: MongoDB, PostgreSQL

Tools: Git, GitHub

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Police Officer | NYPD | New York, NY | 2015 TO 2021

- Conducted witness interviews and gathered details regarding incidents to determine best course of action.
- Make arrests in accordance to state and federal laws.
- Demonstrate clear thinking in high-pressure environments.
- Conducted long term investigations into organized criminal groups with the Violent Crime Squad and Gang Squad.
- Gathered and disseminated raw intelligence for real-time analysis and decision-making.
- Maintained organized records of all information and material pertinent to open investigations.
- Identified potential and existing threats and vulnerabilities.
- Prepared detailed criminal reports of evidence gathered and presented to District Attorney.
- Testified in court to present evidence or acted as a witness in traffic and criminal court.

Residential Concierge | Penmark Realty Corp. | New York, NY | 2013 TO 2015

- Projected a consistent image that complemented the property appearance, performance, and service orientation, while ensuring property rules and regulations were enforced.
- Completed daily shift reports giving a time-stamped overview of what went on during the shift.
- Established relationships with residents to tailor services to their individual needs.
- Monitored fire alarm system and other mechanical equipment while building staff was not on duty.

Assistant Property Manager | The Moinian Group | New York, NY | 2011 TO 2012

- Assisted in managing the day-to-day operations of 6 commercial and residential buildings.
- Communicated with tenants regarding property related issues.
- Coordinated with outside vendors to arrange for maintenance, landscaping, security and other services needed.
- Responded to emergency calls and reported to property manager.

EDUCATION

General Assembly | Software Engineering Immersive | Remote

Masters of Arts in Criminal Justice | CUNY John Jay College | New York, NY